hometechproducts.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Home Tech ProductsHome Tech Products

Hometechproducts.com is committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining a safe online experience for all of our users and customers while providing a quality user experience. Because we gather certain types of information about and from you, our users and customers, in order to fulfill your requests and better serve your needs, you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of this information. This Privacy Policy discloses what information we gather, how we use it, how to correct or change it, and what steps we take to safeguard personal information provided to us both online and offline. Please read the complete Privacy Policy below, as well as our User Agreement, and contact us if you have any questions.

Cookies:

Our Web site uses cookies for the purpose of identifying you when you access your account. This allows us to pre-populate your E-mail address on the login page and to distinguish between your Web session and that of the many other people using our service in and allow us to offer other functionalities (such as screening for age and “recognizing” you to speed up your log-in when you visit our Web site). We may also automatically collect your IP and referring Web site addresses, browser type, domain name and Web site access times (as described below). Our web-based mail service will not function unless your browser is set to accept cookies. You can turn off cookies, but that will affect your online experience.

We use third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number)å about your visits to our Web site in order to provide advertisements on our Web site, other sites and other forms of media about goods and services that may be of interest to you. They may also use this information to track the effectiveness of those ads. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please go to http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp.

Links: Be aware that when you click on ad banners, you may be redirected to other sites not operated by us. You are responsible for information that you provide to these sites. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any site that requests personal information. Note that this policy does not cover the privacy practices of these linked sites.

General Information Collected: When visiting our site, some general information is collected including: IP address (your computer’s unique signature) Operating system (e.g., Windows 95) Browser software (e.g., Microsoft Internet Explorer, Netscape) Internet Service Provider (e.g., Earthlink, Verizon).

The information we collect is aggregated to reflect the population as a whole rather than focused on individuals. We use it to help us better understand the people who visit our Web Site and to continually improve our products and services. In addition, like many other sites with paid advertising, we disclose some of this non- personally identifiable, aggregate information to advertisers to inform them of the number of people who have seen and clicked on their advertisements.

Third Party Service Providers:

Agents and affiliates of hometechproducts.com may occasionally process individual user data as required to provide services for which the user has registered. However, they are not allowed to use this information for any other purpose. All individual user data is owned and controlled by hometechproducts.com. Features on the Web Site that utilize third party service providers include: e-mail notification services and credit card processing. As in any transaction, your credit card company will have all relevant information about the name of the vendor, item(s) purchased, date, total cost and other information necessary to process the transaction. We will not otherwise provide any personal data to your credit card company without your permission.

From time to time we partner with third party service providers to offer additional products and services within the Web Site. To participate in these offerings, you may be asked to provide personal information and agree to terms and conditions relating to the third party service provider. Such requests for information will be displayed and requested by the third party in a straightforward manner with explanation as to whose privacy statement governs the collection of such information. These services include: dating and personals, employment services, home loans, apartment rentals and other services, all of which are purely optional for the user.

Changes to our Privacy Policy:

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy as necessary to protect our users and to comply with best practices employed by other publishers and regulatory organizations across the industry. We recommend that you check the Privacy Policy when you visit our Web Site to be sure that you are aware of and understand our current policy. If we make material changes to this policy, or in how we use or collect your personally identifiable information, we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. We will not make any retroactive material changes in how we handle previously collected personal information unless you allow us to do so, or unless we are legally required to do so, and in such a case we will e-mail registered Web Site visitors information on material changes to this Privacy Policy.

Questions?

For any questions or comments concerning hometechproducts.com’s privacy policy, send an email to: info@hometechproducts.com
